kfp3awesomeadventure.com 2016-10-20

# Privacy Policy - MOM Brands Cereal

### Security

MOM Brands® understands your concerns about online privacy, and we realize that you may have questions about ways we use the information you provide to us during your visit to our web site. We’ve developed and implemented this privacy policy to outline our commitment to protecting the security of your personal information.

As a means of tailoring your experience at our site, MOM Brands gathers non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit our web site. We do not collect personally identifiable information unless you volunteer it.

Our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet, we employ all reasonable measures to ensure the safety of your personal information.

We may on occasion make changes to our privacy policy. Any changes or amendments to our privacy policy will be posted at this URL, effective when posted. Your use of this web site constitutes your acceptance of these terms.

### How We Collect and Use Information

When you visit our site, non-personally identifiable information about you is collected in a number of ways. We track your activities through your IP address, computer settings, or most-recently visited URL. We may also ask you to provide certain non-personally identifiable information about yourself—such as your age, household income, and buying preferences. We use this information to monitor the number of visitors to the various sections of our web site and to tailor your online experience with us—we want to make this site fun and as user-friendly as possible.

MOM Brands does not collect information about you that is personally identifiable unless you voluntarily submit the information to us—for example by filling out a registration form or survey. Our registration forms typically ask for information such as your name, address, zip code, e-mail address and telephone number. Our consumer surveys are designed to collect information about what influences your cereal purchases. We may ask you about your purchase frequency, the importance of various factors in the purchase decision, and how many people, of what ages, live in your household.

In general, we use any personal information you provide to us for the specific purpose we describe (such as mailing address so we can send you free coupons), or for internal marketing purposes. We may also use this information to send you promotional material about MOM Brands, and to assist us in web site administration. You will not be asked to disclose more information than is necessary, and we do not require that you provide this information to access our web site. Any information we collect about you will not be sold to or shared with any third party.

### Use of Cookies

When you view our web site, we might store some information on your computer in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. We use cookies to customize your user interface, speed up the navigation process, and make your web site experience more efficient.

### Children’s Online Privacy

MOM Brands’s web site does not publish content that is targeted to children, nor do we seek to collect personal information from children. Participation in our site and its activities is limited to people 18 years or older, and there are several notices about these participation limits posted on our site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If a specific MOM Brands program allows participation by children, it will be clearly identified as such on our site, and we will comply with all requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. MOM Brands encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children, and to participate in the activities offered on the sites they visit.

### Contacting the Web Site and Choice/Opt-Out and Correct/Update

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Web site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us as noted below. This Web site gives users the following contact options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service and for changing and modifying information previously provided.

**Phone:**  
1-800-743-3029   
Our Consumer Response Center is open weekdays, 8:00am to 4:00pm, CST

**US Mail:**  
MOM Brands  
PO Box 1025  
Lakeville, MN 55044
